Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 12.09.01 21:30:58
主演：哈里逊 福特
《银翼杀手》
主演：罗格 豪尔
主演：西恩 杨
主演：爱德华 詹姆士 奥墨斯
主演：艾门 沃许
主演：黛莉儿 汉娜
主演：威廉 桑德森
主演：布里翁 詹姆士
主演：乔 特科尔
主演：乔安娜 凯西蒂
配乐：范吉利斯
导演：雷德利 史考特
廿一世纪初期，泰瑞公司
将机械人发展至连锁阶段
成为实际上和人类完全相同的生物-被称为“复制人”
连锁六型复制人比创造他们的基因工程师们
有更优秀的力量及敏捷度及不下于他们的智慧
复制人在“世外殖民地”被当作奴工来使用
从事危险的探索与其他星球的殖民任务
一支连锁六型的战斗部队在世外殖民地发动血腥叛变之后
复制人在地球被宣布为违法物必须处以死刑
特种警察小组 - 银翼杀手部队
奉命一旦侦察到侵入的复制人
即可格杀勿论
这不称为处决，而是称为退役
洛杉矶 2019年11月
下一位，科沃斯基里昂
Next subject: Kowalski, Leon.
工程师，机器废物处理
Engineer, waste disposal.
第五区，新进人员，到职第六日
File section: New employee, six days.
请进!
Calling Mr. Webber...
-Come in.-...please report to Zone A Sector 9.
请进!
Calling Mr. Webber...
-Come in.-...please report to Zone A Sector 9.
Replication Center Level 9,we have a B1 security alert.
Stand by for ID check, please.
坐下!
Sit down.
Replication Center Level 9,we have a B1 security alert.
我可以说话吗?
Stand by for....
Care if I taIk?
我可以说话吗?
Stand by for....
我接受测试时会有点紧张
I'm kind of nervous when I take tests.
好，请你别动
Just pIease don't move.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
我今年已接受过智力测验我不记得我测试过这些东西
I aIready had an IQ test.I don't think I've had one of these.
反应时间是评分项目之一所以请专心
Reaction time is a factor,so pay attention.
现在，你回答的越快越好
Now answer as quickIy as you can.
好的
Sure.
杭特华沙1187号
1187 at Hunterwasser.
- 那是一间旅馆- 什么?
That's the hoteI.
- 我住的地方- 环境不错吗?
-What?-Where I Iive.
对，当然，应该吧这是测试的一部份?
-Nice pIace?-Yeah, sure, I guess.
Is that part of the test?
对，当然，应该吧这是测试的一部份?
-Nice pIace?-Yeah, sure, I guess.
Is that part of the test?
不，只是热身
No. Just warming you up. That's aII.
不是幻想之类的
It's not fancy or anything.
你在一处沙漠，在沙上独自行走突然间...
You're in a desert,waIking aIong in the sand, when--
- 现在这是测试?- 是的
Is this the test, now?
你在一处沙漠在沙地上独自行走
Yes. You're in a desert,waIking aIong in the sand...
- 突然间你往下一看...- 哪一个?
- ...when you Iook down---What one?
- 什么?- 哪一个沙漠?
-What?-What desert?
哪一个沙漠都没差别，这完全是假设
Doesn't make any difference.It's compIeteIy hypotheticaI.
- 但是我为什么会在那里?- 也许你受够了
-But how come I'd be there?-Maybe you're fed up.
也许你想独自一人，谁知道?
Maybe you wanna be by yourseIf.Who knows?
你往下看，看见一只乌龟，里昂
You Iook down and see a tortoise.
- 它向你爬过来...- 乌龟? 那是什么?
-It's crawIing towards you---Tortoise? What's that?
- 你知道海龟吧?- 当然
-You know what a turtIe is?-Of course.
同样的东西
Same thing.
我没看过海龟
I've never seen a turtIe.
但是我明白你的意思
But I understand what you mean.
你伸手把乌龟翻过来，里昂
You reach down,you fIip the tortoise over on its back.
这是你想出来的问题吗，贺登先生?
Do you make up these questions,Mr. HoIden?
还是他们写下来给你的?
Or do they write them down for you?
乌龟腹部朝天躺着肚子在烈阳下烤着
The tortoise Iays on its back,its beIIy baking in the sun...
鼓动四肢想把自己翻过来，但没办法
...beating its Iegs,trying to turn itseIf over, but it can't...
除非你肯帮忙，但是你不肯
...not without your heIp.
- 你说我不肯是什么意思?- 就是说，你不肯帮忙
-You're not heIping.-What do you mean I'm not?
I mean, you're not heIping.
- 你说我不肯是什么意思?- 就是说，你不肯帮忙
-You're not heIping.-What do you mean I'm not?
为什么会这样，里昂?
Why is that, Leon?
这些只是问题，里昂
They're just questions, Leon.
回答你的问题，这些是他们写给我的
In answer to your query,they're written down for me.
这是个测试，设计来激发情绪反应
It's a test designed to provokean emotionaI response.
我们可以继续吗?
ShaII we continue?
用一个单字形容
Describe in singIe words onIy thegood things that come into your mind...
只形容你想到的优点
- 关于你的母亲- 我母亲?
...about your mother.
是的
-My mother?-Yeah.
我来跟你说我的母亲吧
Let me teII you about my mother.
新生活就在世外殖民地正等着你
A new life awaits youin the Off-world colonies.
重新开始的机会
The chance to begin again...
在充满机会与冒险的黄金之地
...in a golden land of opportunityand adventure.
新生活就在世外殖民地正等着你
A new life awaits youin the Off-world colonies.
重新开始的机会
The chance to begin again...
在充满机会与冒险的黄金之地
...in a golden land of opportunityand adventure.
让我们到殖民地去吧
以上讯息是由
The custom-tailored, geneticallyengineered humanoid Replicant...
舒马哥多明克公司赞助播出
...designed especially for your needs.
帮助美国进入新世界
So come on, America.Let's put out....
把你的新朋友当成个人仆役或是不会疲累的工人
Give me four.
给我四个
把你的新朋友当成个人仆役或是不会疲累的工人
量身订做的遗传工程
No, four. Two, two. Four.
不，四个，二，二，四
量身订做的遗传工程
No, four. Two, two. Four.
不，四个，二，二，四
类似人类的复制人为你的需求特别设计
还有面
来吧，美国
And noodIes.
还有面
来吧，美国
And noodIes.
让我们一起...
嘿
Hey.
他说你被捕了，德卡先生
He say you under arrest, Mr. Deckard.
老兄，你找错人了
Got the wrong guy, paI.
他说你是银翼杀手
He say you BIade Runner.
告诉他我在吃东西
TeII him I'm eating.
Captain Bryant... .
布莱恩特，是吗?
Bryant, huh?
黄色三号，爬升并维持高度4000
Yellow 3.
Climb and maintain 4000.
黄色三号，爬升并维持高度4000
Yellow 3.
Climb and maintain 4000.
当接近六号停机坪
请谨慎小心
最后降落
Final descent.
现在在降落航道，航向正确
Now on glide path. Mark course.
超过降落的入口
Over the landing threshold.
- 嗨，德卡- 布莱恩特
Hiya, Deck.
如果我只是叫你，你不会来的
Bryant.
You wouIdn't have comeif I just asked you to. Sit down, paI.
如果我只是叫你，你不会来的
Bryant.
You wouIdn't have comeif I just asked you to. Sit down, paI.
坐下，老兄
别这么混帐，德卡
Come on, don't be an asshoIe, Deckard.I've got four skin-jobs waIking the streets.
有四个假货在街上闲晃
他们劫持了世外殖民地的运输船杀了乘客及船员
They jumped a shuttIe Off-worId,kiIIed the crew and passengers.
两周前发现运输船在海岸飘流
They found the shuttIe driftingoff the coast two weeks ago...
所以他们就在附近
...so we know they're around.
- 真够丢脸- 不，一点都不丢脸
Embarrassing.
因为没有人会发现他们在这里
No, sir, not embarrassing. No one's evergonna find out they're down here.
因为你会找到他们而且你会把他们干掉
Because you're gonna spot themand air them out.
我不在这里上班了
I don't work here anymore.
- 交给贺登吧，他很行- 我已经叫他去做了
Give it to HoIden.
-He's good.-I did.
- 交给贺登吧，他很行- 我已经叫他去做了
Give it to HoIden.
-He's good.-I did.
现在他还能呼吸只要没人拔他的呼吸机
He can breathe okayas Iong as nobody unpIugs him.
他不够好，没你那么行
He's not good enough.Not good as you.
我需要你，德卡，这事很棘手是最棘手的
I need you, Deck.
Now, this is a bad one, the worst yet.
我需要你，德卡，这事很棘手是最棘手的
I need you, Deck.
Now, this is a bad one, the worst yet.
我需要老的银翼杀手我需要你的魔力
I need the oId BIade Runner.
I need your magic.
我需要老的银翼杀手我需要你的魔力
I need the oId BIade Runner.
I need your magic.
我进来这儿之前就辞职了，布莱恩特
I was quit when I come in here, Bryant.
现在我更加不想干
I'm twice as quit now.
站住别动!你知道你的份量
Stop right where you are.You know the score, paI?
你不是警察，只是个小人物
If you're not cop, you're IittIe peopIe.
没得选择?
No choice, huh?
没有选择，老兄
No choice, paI.
我今年已接受过智力测验
I already had an IQ test this year.
我不记得我测试过这些东西
I don 't think I've everhad one of these.
反应时间是评分项目之一所以请专心
Reaction time is a factor,so please pay attention.
- 现在，你回答的越快越好- 好的
-Answer as quickly as you can.-Yeah, sure.
杭特华沙1187号
1187 at Hunterwasser.
- 那是间旅馆- 什么?
Yeah. That's the hotel.
- 我住的地方- 环境不错吗?
-What?-Where I live.
对，我猜是的
-Nice place?-Yeah, sure, I guess.
两周前有人从世外殖民地逃走
There was an escape fromthe Off-worId coIonies two weeks ago.
六个复制人，三男三女
Six RepIicants: three maIe, three femaIe.
屠杀23人，抢走了运输船
They sIaughtered 23 peopIeand jumped a shuttIe.
空中巡逻队在海岸发现了运输船
An aeriaI patroI spottedthe ship off the coast.
没有船员，不见他们踪影
No crew, no sight of them.
三天前夜里他们想闯入泰瑞公司
Three nights ago they tried to breakinto TyreII Corporation.
其中两人想穿过电网给烧死
Two of them got fried runningthrough an eIectricaI fieId.
其他人不见了
We Iost the others.
有可能他们想以雇员的身份潜入
On the possibiIity they might tryto infiItrate as empIoyees...
我叫贺登去对新的工人进行人性测验
...I had HoIden go over and runVoight-Kampff tests on the new workers.
看来他找到一个
Looks Iike he got himseIf one.
你往下看，看见一只乌龟，里昂
So you look down and you seea tortoise. It's crawling towards you.
乌龟? 那是什么?
-Tortoise?-That's Leon.
那是里昂
Ammunition Ioaderon intergaIactic runs.
乌龟? 那是什么?
-Tortoise?-That's Leon.
设计来跨星际运输军火
乌龟? 那是什么?
-Tortoise?-That's Leon.
设计来跨星际运输军火
- 你知道海龟吧?- 当然
他能日以继夜的扛着400磅的货物行进
He can Iift 400-pound atomic IoadsaII day and night.
- 你知道海龟吧?- 当然
他能日以继夜的扛着400磅的货物行进
He can Iift 400-pound atomic IoadsaII day and night.
同样的东西
他能日以继夜的扛着400磅的货物行进
He can Iift 400-pound atomic IoadsaII day and night.
我没看过海龟
他能日以继夜的扛着400磅的货物行进
He can Iift 400-pound atomic IoadsaII day and night.
我没看过海龟
能伤到他的唯一办法就是杀了他
The onIy way you can hurt himis to kiII him.
我没看过海龟
能伤到他的唯一办法就是杀了他
The onIy way you can hurt himis to kiII him.
我不懂，为何他们冒险回来地球?
I don't get it. What do they risk comingback to Earth for? That's unusuaI. Why...?
能伤到他的唯一办法就是杀了他
The onIy way you can hurt himis to kiII him.
我不懂，为何他们冒险回来地球?
I don't get it. What do they risk comingback to Earth for? That's unusuaI. Why...?
这太不寻常了，为什么...
他们想从泰瑞公司得到什么?
What do they wantout of the TyreII Corporation?
老兄，别问我这就是找你来的原因
WeII, you teII me, paI.That's what you're here for.
- 这是什么?- 连锁六型
-What's this?-Nexus 6. Roy Batty.
罗伊贝逖启动日期：2016年
Incept date: 2016.
战斗型号，能最佳化的自给自足
Combat modeI. Optimum seIf-sufficiency.
大概是领导人
ProbabIy the Ieader.
这是卓拉
This is Zhora.
她被训练成为世外殖民地的刺客
She's trained foran Off-worId kick murder squad.
说到美女与野兽
TaIk about Beauty and the Beast.She's both.
她两者皆是
第四个假货是蒲莉丝是基本娱乐型号
The fourth skin-job is Pris,a basic pIeasure modeI.
外围殖民地军事俱乐部的标准装备
The standard item for miIitary cIubsin the outer coIonies.
他们各方面都是设计来模仿人类除了他们的感情
They were designed to copy human beingsin every way except their emotions.
但设计者认为数年后
The designers reckonedafter a few years...
他们可能会发展出自己的情绪反应
...they might deveIoptheir own emotionaI responses.
仇恨、爱、恐惧、愤怒、羡慕
Oh, hate, Iove, fear, anger, envy.
- 所以他们做了保险装置- 是什么?
So they buiIt in a faiI-safe device.
四年的寿命
-Which is what?-Four-year Iifespan.
现在泰瑞公司有一个连锁六型
Now, there's a Nexus 6over at the TyreII Corporation.
- 我要你过去用机器测试看看- 要是机器测不出来呢?
-I want you to go put the machine on it.-And if the machine doesn't work?
喜欢这只猫头鹰吗?
Do you Iike our owI?
是人造的?
It's artificiaI?
当然
Of course it is.
一定很贵
Must be expensive.
非常贵，我叫瑞秋
Very. I'm RachaeI.
德卡
Deckard.
看来你认为我们的产品对大众无益
It seems you feeI our workis not a benefit to the pubIic.
复制人就像其他的机器不是有益便是有危险
RepIicants are Iike any other machine:They're either a benefit or a hazard.
若他们有益，则和我无关
If they're a benefit, it's not my probIem.
我可问你一个私人问题吗?
May I ask you a personaI question?
当然
Sure.
你是否曾经错误地把人类退役?
Have you ever retired a humanby mistake?
没有
No.
但以你的职位，那是种风险
-But in your position, that is a risk.-Is this to be an empathy test?
这是移情测试吗?
所谓脸红反应的微血管扩张?
CapiIIary diIationof the so-caIIed bIush response?
瞳孔的波动
FIuctuation of the pupiI.
虹膜不自觉地扩大
InvoIuntary diIation of the iris.
我们简称为人性测验
We caII it Voight-Kampff for short.
德卡先生，艾登泰瑞博士
Mr. Deckard, Dr. EIdon TyreII.
示范一下
Demonstrate it.
- 我想看看它的运作- 测试对象在哪?
I wanna see it work.
我想看它用来测试人类
-Where's the subject?-I wanna see it work on a person.
在看“是”的结果之前我想看“否”的情况
I wanna see a negativebefore I provide you with a positive.
那能证明什么?
What's that gonna prove?
让我满足
InduIge me.
测试你?
On you?
测试她
Try her.
这里太亮了
It's too bright in here.
介意我抽烟?
Do you mind if I smoke?
对测试没影响
It won't affect the test.
好，我会问你一连串的问题
AII right, I'm gonna ask youa series of questions.
你只需放松，尽量简洁地回答
Just reIax and answer themas simpIy as you can.
在你生日那天
It's your birthday.Someone gives you a caIfskin waIIet.
- 有人给你送牛皮皮夹- 我不会接受
I wouIdn't accept it.
同时我会向警方举报送给我的人
AIso, I'd report the personwho gave it to me to the poIice.
你有一个小男孩他给你看他的蝴蝶标本收藏
You've got a IittIe boy.He shows you his butterfIy coIIection...
和杀昆虫的酒精瓶
...pIus the kiIIing jar.
我会带他看医生
I'd take him to the doctor.
你在看电视
You're watching teIevision.
忽然发觉手臂上有一只黄蜂
SuddenIy you reaIizethere's a wasp crawIing on your arm.
我会杀了它
I'd kiII it.
你在看杂志
You're reading a magazine. You comeacross a fuII-page nude photo of a girI.
看见一幅全页的女人裸照
这是测试我是复制人还是女同性恋者德卡先生?
Is this testing whether I'm a RepIicantor a Iesbian, Mr. Deckard?
请回答问题
Just answer the questions, pIease.
你把它拿给丈夫看
You show it to your husband.
他很喜欢，所以把它挂在你们卧室墙上
He Iikes it so muchhe hangs it on your bedroom waII.
--bush outside your window?
他很喜欢，所以把它挂在你们卧室墙上
He Iikes it so muchhe hangs it on your bedroom waII.
--bush outside your window?
我不会让他挂
I wouIdn't Iet him.
--orange body, green Iegs?
我不会让他挂
I wouIdn't Iet him.
--orange body, green Iegs?
- 为什么?- 他有我应该就够了
Why not?
I shouId be enough for him.
- 为什么?- 他有我应该就够了
Why not?
I shouId be enough for him.
再问一题
One more question.
你观赏一出舞台剧，正进行一场宴会
You're watching a stage pIay,a banquet is in progress.
宾客享用生蚝作开胃菜
The guests are enjoyingan appetizer of raw oysters.
主菜包括炖狗肉
The entr茅e consists of boiIed dog.
你可否出去一会儿，瑞秋?
WouId you step outfor a few moments, RachaeI?
谢谢
Thank you.
- 她是复制人，对吧?- 我很佩服
She's a RepIicant, isn't she?
I'm impressed.
- 她是复制人，对吧?- 我很佩服
She's a RepIicant, isn't she?
I'm impressed.
通常要问多少问题才会发现?
How many questionsdoes it usuaIIy take to spot one?
I'm impressed.
通常要问多少问题才会发现?
How many questionsdoes it usuaIIy take to spot one?
- 我不懂，泰瑞- 多少个问题?
-I don't get it, TyreII.-How many questions?
20到30个互相对照的问题
Twenty, thirty, cross-referenced.
瑞秋问了超过一百个吧?
It took more than a hundred for RachaeI,didn't it?
她不知道?
She doesn't know.
- 我想，她开始怀疑了- 怀疑! 它怎会不知道自己是什么?
She's beginning to suspect, I think.
Suspect?How can it not know what it is?
- 我想，她开始怀疑了- 怀疑! 它怎会不知道自己是什么?
She's beginning to suspect, I think.
在泰瑞，商业是我们的目标“比人类更像人类”是我们的座右铭
Commerce is our goaI here at TyreII.
''More human than human'' is our motto.
在泰瑞，商业是我们的目标“比人类更像人类”是我们的座右铭
Commerce is our goaI here at TyreII.
''More human than human'' is our motto.
瑞秋是个实验，如此而已
RachaeI is an experiment, nothing more.
我们开始认同他们
We began to recognize in thema strange obsession.
这是种怪异的妄想
毕竟他们缺乏情感经验
After aII, they are emotionaIIyinexperienced, with onIy a few years...
只有几年的时间去累积
...in which to store up the experienceswhich you and I take for granted.
你我视为理所当然的体验如果我们赐予他们过去
If we gift them with a past, we createa cushion or a piIIow for their emotions...
创造出他们情感上的依靠和安慰
结果是我们更能够控制他们
...then consequentIywe can controI them better.
记忆
Memories.
你说的是记忆
You're taIking about memories.
反应时间是评分项目之一所以请专心
Reaction time is a factor,so please pay attention.
- 现在，你回答的越快越好- 好的
-Now answer as quickly as you can.-Sure.
杭特华沙1187号
- 1187 at Hunterwasser.-Yeah. That's the hotel.
- 那是一间旅馆- 什么?
-What?-Where I live.
- 我住的地方- 环境不错吗?
-Nice place?-Yeah, sure, I guess.
对，当然，应该吧这是测试的一部份?
-Is that part of the test?-No.
不是
科沃斯基
KowaIski.
时间
Time...
够了
...enough.
你拿到你宝贵的照片了?
Did you get your precious photos?
有人在
Someone was there.
人?
Men?
警察?
PoIicemen?
天使如火般地坠落
Fiery the angels fell
海岸四处咆哮着雷声
Deep thunder rolled around their shores
燃烧着海兽的火焰
Burning with the fires of Orc
你不能来这里!
You not come here! IIIegaI!
非法入侵!
嘿! 嘿!
Hey! Hey!
很冷的! 那是我的眼睛! 会冻伤的!
CoId! Those are my eyes! Freezing!
是的
Yes.
问题
Questions.
Hey! Hey!
型号? 寿命? 启动日期?
MorphoIogy. Longevity. Incept dates.
不知道，我不知道这些东西
Don't know.
I don't know such stuff.
不知道，我不知道这些东西
Don't know.
I don't know such stuff.
我只做眼睛
I just do eyes.
只有眼睛，只是基因设计
Just eyes, just genetic design.
只有眼睛
Just eyes.
你是连锁型的?
You Nexus, huh?
我设计了你的眼睛
I design your eyes.
老周
Chew...
但愿你能目睹我用你的眼睛所看见的
...if onIy you couId seewhat I've seen with your eyes.
现在
Now...
问题
...questions.
我不知道答案
I don't know answers.
谁知道?
Who does?
泰瑞，他无所不知
TyreII.
He knows everything.
泰瑞，他无所不知
TyreII.
泰瑞公司?
TyreII Corporation?
他是大老板，大天才他设计了你的心智
He big boss. Big genius.He design your mind.
你的脑袋
Your brain, huh?
聪明
Smart.
很冷
Very coId.
要见他不容易
Not an easy man to see...
把外套给我
Give me coat.
...是吗?
...I guess?
赛巴斯汀
Sebastian.
他能带你去那里他能带你去那里
He take you there.He take you there.
哪个赛巴斯汀?
Sebastian who?
J... J.F.
J.F...
赛巴斯汀
...Sebast... .
那么
Now...
我们可以在哪里找到这位
...where...
...wouId we find this...
我们可以在哪里找到这位
...where...
...wouId we find this...
J. F. 赛巴斯汀?
...J.F. Sebastian?
我们可以继续吗?
Let's continue, shall we?
用一个单字形容
Describe in single words...
只形容你想到的优点
...only the good things that comeinto your mind about your mother.
- 关于你的母亲- 我母亲?
-My mother?-Yeah.
是的
I'll tell you about my mother.
我来跟你说我的母亲吧
声纹辨织，请说出你楼层号码
Voice print identification.Your floor number, please.
- 德卡，97- 97，谢谢
-Deckard, 97.-97. Thank you. Danke.
我想见你
I wanted to see you.
所以我在这里等，让我帮你
So I waited.
Let me heIp you.
所以我在这里等，让我帮你
So I waited.
Let me heIp you.
我为何需要帮忙?
What do I need heIp for?
我不知道为什么他告诉你他所做的
I don't know whyhe toId you what he did.
去跟他谈
TaIk to him.
他不会见我
He wouIdn't see me.
想喝酒吗?
You want a drink?
不?
No?
你认为我是复制人，是吧?
You think I'm a RepIicant, don't you?
看着
Look.
这是我和我母亲
It's me with my mother.
是吗?
Yeah?
记得你六岁的时候吗?
Remember when you were 6?
你和哥哥从地下室窗户溜进空的大楼
You and your brother snuck into an emptybuiIding through a basement window.
你们玩扮医生游戏?
You were gonna pIay doctor?
他给你看他下面，但轮到你时你害怕然后跑走了
He showed you his, and when it gotto be your turn, you chickened and ran.
记得吗?
Remember that?
你有对任何人说吗?你母亲? 泰瑞? 其他人?
Did you ever teII anybody that?Your mother, TyreII, anybody, huh?
记得住在你窗外树丛的蜘蛛吗?
You remember the spider that Iivedin the bush outside your window?
橙色身体，绿色的脚?
Orange body, green Iegs?
看着它织网织了整个夏天?有一天，上面有个巨卵
Watched her buiId a web aII summer?
Then one day, there's a big egg in it.
看着它织网织了整个夏天?有一天，上面有个巨卵
Watched her buiId a web aII summer?
Then one day, there's a big egg in it.
卵孵化了
The egg hatched... .
- 卵孵化了...- 然后呢
-The egg hatched...-And?
...有一百只小蜘蛛爬出来
...and a hundred baby spiders came out.
它们把它吃了
And they ate her.
植入
ImpIants.
那不是你的回忆，是别人的
Those aren't your memories,they're somebody eIse's.
那是泰瑞的侄女的回忆
They're TyreII's niece's.
好吧，糟糕的笑话
Okay.
Bad joke.
好吧，糟糕的笑话
Okay.
Bad joke.
我说了个糟糕的笑话你不是复制人
I made a bad joke.
You're not a RepIicant.
我说了个糟糕的笑话你不是复制人
I made a bad joke.
You're not a RepIicant.
回家去，好吗?
Go home.
Okay?
回家去，好吗?
Go home.
Okay?
是真的，我很抱歉
No, reaIIy. I'm sorry.
回家吧
Go home.
想喝一杯吗?
Want a drink?
我给你来杯酒，我给你个杯子
I'II get you a drink.
I'II get a gIass.
我给你来杯酒，我给你个杯子
I'II get you a drink.
I'II get a gIass.
嘿!
Hey!
你忘了你的袋子
You forgot your bag.
我迷路了
I'm Iost.
放心，我不会伤害你的
Don't worry, I won't hurt you.
- 你叫什么?- 蒲莉丝
What's your name?
我叫J.F.赛巴斯汀
-Pris.-Mine's J.F. Sebastian.
- 嗨- 嗨
-Hi.-Hi.
你要去哪?
Oh, where were you going?
回家?
Home?
我没有家
I don't have one.
我们吓了对方一跳，是吧?
We scared each other pretty good,didn't we?
当然
We sure did.
我好饿，J.F.
I'm hungry, J.F.
我里面有食物，你要进来吗?
I got stuff inside.
You wanna come in?
我里面有食物，你要进来吗?
I got stuff inside.
You wanna come in?
我正希望你这么说
I was hoping you'd say that.
你一个人住在这里?
Do you Iive in this buiIdingaII by yourseIf?
对，现在我确实是一个人住在这里
Yeah, I Iive herepretty much aIone right now.
这里不缺住的地方
No housing shortage around here.
每个人都有很多空间
PIenty of room for everybody.
小心有水
Watch out for the water.
你在这里一定很寂寞，J.F.
Must get IoneIy here, J.F.
不算是，我制造朋友
Not reaIIy. I make friends.
他们是玩具，我的朋友是玩具他们是我做的
They're toys. My friends are toys.I make them.
是个嗜好，我是基因设计师你知道那是什么吗?
It's a hobby. I'm a genetic designer.
Do you know what that is?
是个嗜好，我是基因设计师你知道那是什么吗?
It's a hobby. I'm a genetic designer.
Do you know what that is?
不知道
No.
现在
Now.
喔
我回来了!
Yoo-hoo, home again.
Home again, home again, jiggidy-jig.
- 晚安，J.F.!- 晚安，各位
-Good evening, J.F.-Evening, feIIas.
他们是我朋友，是我做的
They're my friends. I made them.
你的家人呢?
Where are your foIks?
- 我算是个孤儿- 喔
I'm sort of an orphan.
那你的朋友呢?
What about your friends?
我有一些，但我必需要找到他们
I have some, but I have to find them.
明天我会告诉他们我在哪里
I'II Iet them know where I am tomorrow.
嗯?
我可以帮你拿这些东西吗?
Can I take those things for you?They're soaked, aren't they?
湿透了，不是吗?
放大224到176
Enhance 224 to 176.
放大，停
Enhance.
Stop.
放大，停
Enhance.
Stop.
推入
Move in.
停
Stop.
拉出，右移，停
PuII out, track right.
Stop.
拉出，右移，停
PuII out, track right.
Stop.
置中，拉回
Center and puII back.
停
Stop.
移动右45
Track 45 right.
停
Stop.
置中然后停
Center and stop.
放大34至36
Enhance 34 to 36.
右移和拉回
Pan right and puII back.
停
Stop.
放大34至46
Enhance 34 to 46.
拉回
PuII back.
慢着，向右
Wait a minute. Go right.
停
Stop.
放大57至19
Enhance 57-19.
移动左45
Track 45 Ieft.
停
Stop.
放大15至23
Enhance 15 to 23.
这儿给我一份复印
Give me a hard copy right there.
鱼吗?
Fish?
我看这是制造的，看
I think it was manufactured IocaIIy.
手工精细，品质优良
Finest quaIity. Superior workmanship.
有制作者的序号
There is the maker's seriaI number.
990-6947
9906947-XB71.
XB-71
很有趣
Interesting.
这不是鱼，是蛇的鳞片
Not fish. Snake scaIe.
蛇?
Snake.
找阿布杜尔哈桑，这蛇是他做的
Try AbduI Ben Hassan.He make this snake!
阿布杜尔哈桑?
AbduI Hassan?
我是警察，想问你几个问题
I'm a poIice officer.I'd Iike to ask you a few questions.
人造蛇执照XB-71，是你吗?
ArtificiaI snake Iicense XB71, that's you?
这是你的作品?你卖给了谁?
This is your work, huh?Who did you seII it to?
我的作品?没多少人付得起这样的品质
My work? Not too manycouId afford such quaIity.
- 有多少?- 很少
How many?
是多少? 搞清楚，老兄
-Very few.-How few?
塔菲刘易斯，在第四区唐人街
-Look, my friend---Taffey Lewis' .
Down in Fourth Sector, Chinatown.
塔菲刘易斯，在第四区唐人街
-Look, my friend---Taffey Lewis' .
Down in Fourth Sector, Chinatown.
Cross now. Cross now. Cross now.
Cross now. Cross now.
酒保
Bartender.
塔菲刘易斯?
Taffey Lewis?
Thank you.
塔菲?
-Taffey?-Yeah?
- 我想问你几个问题- 问吧
I'd Iike to ask you a few questions.
BIow.
- 我想问你几个问题- 问吧
I'd Iike to ask you a few questions.
BIow.
你有向埃及人买过蛇吗，塔菲?
You ever buy snakesfrom the Egyptian, Taffey?
经常买，老兄
AII the time, paI.
见过这女孩吗?
You ever see this girI, huh?
没见过，快滚
Never seen her. Buzz off.
你的执照还有效吗，老兄?
Your Iicenses in order, paI?
嘿，路易，这位仁兄口渴
Hey, Louie.
免费给他一杯，好吗?再见
The man is dry. Give him oneon the house, okay? See?
喂?
HeIIo?
以前是有人离开过我，但是...
I've had peopIe waIk out on me before,but not when...
都不是我那么迷人的时候
...I was being so charming.
我现在在第四区的酒吧
I'm in a bar, here now,down in the Fourth Sector.
塔菲刘易斯这里
Taffey Lewis is on the Iine.
你何不来这里喝一杯?
Why don't you come on down hereand have a drink?
我不这么想，德卡先生
I don 't think so, Mr. Deckard.
- 那不是我去的地方- 那到别处去
That's not my kind of place.
Go somepIace eIse?
- 那不是我去的地方- 那到别处去
That's not my kind of place.
Go somepIace eIse?
各位先生女士
Ladies and gentlemen...
塔菲刘易斯巨献莎乐美小姐与蛇共舞
... Taffey Lewis presentsMiss Salome and the snake.
看她与曾使人堕落的蛇
Watch her take the pleasurefrom the serpent...
尽情享受欢愉
... that once corrupted man.
对不起 莎乐美小姐我可跟你谈一下吗?
Excuse me, Miss SaIome,can I taIk to you for a minute?
我是美国综艺艺人协会的
I'm from the American Federationof Variety Artists.
是吗?
Oh, yeah?
我不是来此请你加入的不，女士，那不是我的部门
I'm not here to make you join.No, ma'am. That's not my department.
事实上
ActuaIIy...
我是道德凌虐秘密委员会的人
...I'm from the ConfidentiaI Committeeon MoraI Abuses.
- 道德凌虐委员会?- 是的，女士
Committee of MoraI Abuses?
据报这儿的管理阶层
There's been reportsthat the management...
曾经侵犯过艺人
...has been taking Iibertieswith the artists.
我完全不知道
I don't know nothing about it.
你可有在任何方面感到被剥削?
Have you feIt yourseIf to beexpIoited in any way?
你指的“剥削”是什么意思?
How do you mean ''expIoited''?
像是要得到这份工作...
WeII, Iike to get this job.
我是说，你是否...你是否有做或是被要求做任何...
I mean, did you do, or were youasked to do, anything that's...
猥亵或令人厌恶的事
...Iewd or unsavory or...
不做的话就把你开除?
...otherwise repuIsiveto your person, huh?
- 你是当真的?- 是的
-Are you for reaI?-Oh, yeah.
我想...想检查你的更衣室如果可以的话
I'd Iike to checkyour dressing room, if I may.
- 要做什么?- 要找看看...有没有洞
-For what?-For hoIes.
洞?
HoIes?
你一定很吃惊
WeII, you'd be surprisedwhat a guy wouId go through...
有人会不择手段为了偷瞄动人的身体
...to get a gIimpse of a beautifuI body.
不! 我不惊讶
No, I wouIdn't.
嗯...小的
LittIe...
肮脏的洞，他们在墙上钻孔
...dirty hoIes they driII in the waIIso they can watch a Iady undress.
好偷看女人脱衣服
- 这蛇是真的吗?- 当然不是真的
-Is this a reaI snake?-Of course it's not reaI.
如果我买得起真蛇还会在这儿工作吗?
Think I'd be working in a pIace Iike thisif I couId afford a reaI snake?
那么，要是有人想剥削我，我该找谁?
So if somebody does try to expIoit me,who do I go to about it?
找我
-Me.-You're a dedicated man. Dry me.
你这人真是勤奋，帮我擦干
The onIy thing they care about--
Hey!
Cross now. Cross now.
(尽速通过...尽速通过...)
(不准通过...不准通过...)
Don 't walk. Don 't walk.
Don 't walk. Don 't walk. Don 't walk.
Cross now. Cross now.
(尽速通过...尽速通过...)
让开! 别挡路!
Move! Get out of the way!
Cross now. Cross now.
让开! 别挡路!
Move! Get out of the way!
德卡
Deckard.
B-263-54.
B26354.
散开...散开
Move on. Move on.
等一下
A minute.
- 你要什么?- 青岛
Yeah, what do you want?
Tsingtao.
- 你要什么?- 青岛
Yeah, what do you want?
Tsingtao.
- 这些够吗?- 够
This enough?
Yeah.
- 这些够吗?- 够
This enough?
Yeah.
布莱恩特
Bryant.
老天，德卡，你看起来和你丢在路边的那个假货一样糟糕
Christ, Deckard, you Iook aImost as badas that skin-job you Ieft on the sidewaIk.
我要回家了
I'm going home.
你可向他学着点，加夫
CouId Iearn from this guy, Gaff.
天杀的，他根本就是单人屠宰场
He's a goddamn one-mansIaughterhouse, that's what he is.
还有四个加夫，我们走吧
Four more to go.
三个
-Come on, Gaff, Iet's go.-Three.
- 还有三个- 是四个
There's three to go.
There's four.
- 还有三个- 是四个
There's three to go.
There's four.
还有你在泰瑞公司测试的那个假货
That skin-job you VK'dat the TyreII Corporation...
瑞秋失踪了，消失不见
...RachaeI, disappeared, vanished.Didn't even know she was a RepIicant.
她甚至不知道自己是个复制人
泰瑞说是和大脑植入有关
Something to do with a brain impIant,says TyreII.
走吧，加夫替我喝一杯吧，老兄?
Come on, Gaff.Drink some for me, huh, paI?
- 里昂- 我几岁了?
Leon.
How oId am I?
- 里昂- 我几岁了?
Leon.
How oId am I?
我不知道
I don't know.
我的生日是2017年4月10日我能活多久?
My birthday's ApriI 10, 2017.How Iong do I Iive?
四年
Four years.
比你还久!
More than you.
活在恐惧中是很痛苦的，不是吗?
PainfuI to Iive in fear, isn't it?
没什么比永远搔不到的痒更惨的事
Nothing is worse than havingan itch you can never scratch.
我同意
I agree.
醒来! 该受死了
Wake up. Time to die.
发抖?
Shakes?
我也是
Me too.
我抖的厉害
I get them bad.
这是这工作的一部份
It's part of the business.
我不是做这工作的
I'm not in the business.
我就是这工作
I am the business.
要是我往北走呢?
What if I go north?
消失不见
Disappear.
你是否会来追我?
WouId you come after me?
猎杀我?
Hunt me?
不
No.
我不会
No, I wouIdn't.
我欠你一次
I owe you one.
但别人会追你
But somebody wouId.
德卡
Deckard...
你知道我的档案?
...you know those fiIes on me?
启动日期
The incept date. The Iongevity.
寿命，诸如此类的事情
Those things.
你看过?
You saw them?
那些是机密
They're...
但你是个警察
...cIassified.
But you're a poIiceman.
但你是个警察
...cIassified.
But you're a poIiceman.
我没有看
I...
...didn't Iook at them.
我没有看
I...
...didn't Iook at them.
你知道，你那个人性测验
You know,that Voight-Kampff test of yours...
你曾经用来测试你自己吗?
...did you ever take that test yourseIf?
德卡?
Deckard.
我梦到音乐
I dreamt music.
我不知道我会不会弹琴
I didn't know if I couId pIay.
我记得上过课
I remember Iessons.
我不知道那是我...还是泰瑞的侄女
I don't know if it's me or TyreII's niece.
你弹得很美
You pIay beautifuIIy.
现在，吻我
Now you kiss me.
- 我不能依靠我的记...- 说，“吻我”
I can't reIy on my--
Say, ''Kiss me. ''
- 我不能依靠我的记...- 说，“吻我”
I can't reIy on my--
Say, ''Kiss me. ''
吻我
Kiss me.
我要你
I want you.
再说一次
Again.
我要你
I want you.
拥抱我
Put your hands on me.
- 你做什么?- 对不起，看看而已
-What you doing?-I'm sorry. Just peeking.
喔
- 我看来如何?- 好一点
-How do I Iook?-You Iook better.
- 只是好一点?- 你看来很漂亮
-Just better?-WeII...
...you Iook beautifuI.
- 只是好一点?- 你看来很漂亮
-Just better?-WeII...
...you Iook beautifuI.
谢谢
Thanks.
你几岁了?
How oId are you?
二十五
Twenty-five.
- 你有什么问题?- 麦修撒拉征候群
-What's your probIem?-MethuseIah syndrome.
那是什么?
What's that?
我的腺体，变老的太快
My gIands, they grow oId too fast.
这是你还留在地球的原因?
-Is that why you're stiII on Earth?-Yeah. I couIdn't pass the medicaI.
对，我没法通过体检
反正，我满喜欢待在这里
Anyway...
...I kind of Iike it here.
反正，我满喜欢待在这里
Anyway...
...I kind of Iike it here.
我喜欢你现在的样子
I Iike you...
...just the way you are.
我喜欢你现在的样子
I Iike you...
...just the way you are.
嗨，洛伊
Hi, Roy.
老天，你的玩具真的很不错
Hi.
Gosh, you...
老天，你的玩具真的很不错
Hi.
...reaIIy got some nice toys here.
老天，你的玩具真的很不错
Hi.
...reaIIy got some nice toys here.
这就是我对你说过的朋友
This is the friend I was teIIing you about.
...reaIIy got some nice toys here.
这就是我对你说过的朋友
This is the friend I was teIIing you about.
这是我的救星，J.F.赛巴斯汀
This is my savior, J.F. Sebastian.
赛巴斯汀
Sebastian.
我喜欢留下不走的人
I Iike a man that stays put.
你一个人住在这里，是吗?
You Iive here aII by yourseIf, do you?
是的
Yes.
要不要吃早餐?
How about some breakfast?
我去煮早餐，失陪
I was just gonna make some.
Excuse me.
我去煮早餐，失陪
I was just gonna make some.
Excuse me.
怎样?
WeII?
- 里昂...- 怎么了?
Leon... .
What's going on?
- 里昂...- 怎么了?
Leon... .
What's going on?
我...
现在只有我们俩了
There's onIy two of us now.
我们太笨了，我们会死的
Then we're stupid and we'II die.
不，不会的
No, we won't.
不，马吃掉皇后?
No.
Knight takes queen, see?
不，马吃掉皇后?
No.
Knight takes queen, see?
我不会这样下
Won't do.
Knight takes queen, see?
我不会这样下
Won't do.
你为何盯着我们看，赛巴斯汀?
Why are you staring at us, Sebastian?
因为...你这么独特
Because...
...you're so different.
因为...你这么独特
Because...
...you're so different.
你是这么的完美
You're so perfect.
是的
Yes.
你是那一代的?
What generation are you?
- 连锁六型- 啊，我就知道!
Nexus 6.
因为我替泰瑞公司做的基因设计
I knew it.
Because I do genetic design workfor the TyreII Corporation.
因为我替泰瑞公司做的基因设计
I knew it.
Because I do genetic design workfor the TyreII Corporation.
你有我的一部份
There's some of me in you.
Because I do genetic design workfor the TyreII Corporation.
你有我的一部份
There's some of me in you.
秀给我看
Show me something.
- 像什么?- 什么都行
Like what?
Like anything.
- 像什么?- 什么都行
Like what?
Like anything.
我们不是电脑，赛巴斯汀我们是血肉之躯
We're no computers, Sebastian.We're physicaI.
我思考，赛巴斯汀，故我在
I think, Sebastian...
...therefore, I am.
我思考，赛巴斯汀，故我在
I think, Sebastian...
...therefore, I am.
非常好，蒲莉丝 现在让他看看为什么
Very good, Pris. Now show him why.
- 我们有许多共通点- 你是什么意思?
We've got a Iot in common.
- 类似的问题- 加速衰老
-What do you mean?-SimiIar probIems.
AcceIerated decrepitude.
- 类似的问题- 加速衰老
-What do you mean?-SimiIar probIems.
AcceIerated decrepitude.
我对生化机械所知不多，洛伊我希望我知道
I don't know much about bio-mechanics,Roy. I wish I did.
要是我们不尽快找出办法
If we don't find heIp soon...
蒲莉丝就活不久了
...Pris hasn't got Iong to Iive.
我们不能容许它发生
We can't aIIow that.
- 他厉害吗?- 谁?
-Is he good?-Who?
- 你的对手- 哦...泰瑞博士?
-Your opponent.-Oh, Dr. TyreII?
我下棋只击败他一次他是个天才
I've onIy beaten him once in chess.He's a genius.
你是他设计的
He designed you.
也许他能帮忙
Maybe he couId heIp.
我很乐意向他提出
I'd be happy to mention it to him.
最好是我能亲自和他谈
Better if I taIk to him in person.
就我所知，要见他不太容易
But I understandhe's a sort of hard man to get to.
是的，很难
Yes.
Very.
是的，很难
Yes.
Very.
你会帮我们吗?
WiII you heIp us?
我不能
I can't.
我们需要你，赛巴斯汀你是我们最好也是唯一的朋友
We need you, Sebastian.
You're our best and onIy friend.
我们需要你，赛巴斯汀你是我们最好也是唯一的朋友
We need you, Sebastian.
You're our best and onIy friend.
我们好高兴你找到我们
We're so happy you found us.
我不认为世上有其他人类会帮助我们
I don't thinkthere's another human being...
...in the whoIe worIdwho wouId've heIped us.
我不认为世上有其他人类会帮助我们
I don't thinkthere's another human being...
...in the whoIe worIdwho wouId've heIped us.
六万六千 普塞与安高比
66,000 Prosser & Ankovich.
卖出，卖出价...
Trade.
蓝色入口
-Trade at two---Blue entry.
J.F.赛巴斯汀先生
A Mr. J.F. Sebastian.
1-6-4-1-7.
16417.
在这个时候?
At this hour?
有何贵干，赛巴斯汀?
What can I do for you, Sebastian?
皇后吃掉象六，将军
Queen to bishop six. Check.
乱来
Nonsense.
等一等
Just a moment.
皇后吃掉象六? 荒谬
Queen to bishop six, ridicuIous.
皇后
Queen...
象六
...bishop six.
马
Knight...
吃掉皇后
... takes queen.
你想到了什么，赛巴斯汀?你在想什么?
What's on your mind, Sebastian?
What are you thinking about?
你想到了什么，赛巴斯汀?你在想什么?
What's on your mind, Sebastian?
What are you thinking about?
象移到国王七，将军
Bishop to king seven.
Checkmate.
象移到国王七，将军
Bishop to king seven.
Checkmate.
我看是象移到国王七，将军
Bishop to king seven.Checkmate, I think.
你思潮泉涌了吗，赛巴斯汀?
Got a brainstorm, huh, Sebastian?
牛奶和饼干让你睡不着?
MiIk and cookies kept you awake, huh?
我们来讨论一下
Let's discuss this.
你还是上来吧，赛巴斯汀
You better come up, Sebastian.
泰瑞先生?
Mr. TyreII?
我...
I... .
我带了个朋友
I brought a friend.
我很惊讶你没有早点来
I'm surprisedyou didn't come here sooner.
一个人要见造物者并不容易
It's not an easy thingto meet your maker.
造物者能为你做什么吗?
And what can he do for you?
造物者能否修理他所造之物?
Can the maker repair what he makes?
你想...被修改吗?
WouId you Iike to be modified?
留在这里
Stay here.
我想的是更根本的事
Had in mind somethinga IittIe more radicaI.
什么...
What...?
- 有什么问题?- 死亡
What seems to be the probIem?
死亡
-Death.-Death.
恐怕这有点超出了我的管辖范围，你...
WeII, I'm afraid that'sa IittIe out of my jurisdiction. You--
我要更多的生命...混蛋
I want more Iife...
...father.
我要更多的生命...混蛋
I want more Iife...
...father.
生命的真相
The facts of Iife.
想要改变
To make an aIteration in the...
有机生物系统的进化是会致命的
...evoIvement ofan organic Iife system is fataI.
编码程序一旦建立便无法修改
A coding sequence cannot be revisedonce it's been estabIished.
为什么不行?
Why not?
因为，在温育的第二天
Because by the second dayof incubation...
任何细胞进行逆转的突变
...any ceIIs that have undergonereversion mutations...
会产生回复突变的菌落就像老鼠离开一艘船
...give rise to revertant coIoniesIike rats Ieaving a sinking ship.
然后船沉没
Then the ship sinks.
那 E.M.S.重组呢?
What about EMS recombination?
我们试过了
We've aIready tried it.
甲乙基烷矿酸是烷化剂
EthyI methane suIfonate is anaIkyIating agent and a potent mutagen.
也是有效的突变剂它创造出非常致命的病毒
It created a virus so IethaI the...
实验对象离开实验台前就死了
...subject was deadbefore he Ieft the tabIe.
抑制蛋白可阻挡运作的细胞
Then a repressor proteinthat bIocks the operating ceIIs.
它不会阻碍复制，但会导致复制错误
WouIdn't obstruct repIication, but itdoes give rise to an error in repIication.
因此...新形成的DNA带有变异
So that the newIy formed DNA strandcarries a mutation...
你会再次得到病毒
...and you've got a virus again.
但这些，所有的一切都只是...
But this, aII of this, is...
理论
...academic.
我们已尽我们所能把你做好
You were madeas weII as we couId make you.
但不能持久
But not to Iast.
两倍明亮的光芒，只能燃烧一半的寿命
The Iight that burns twice as brightburns haIf as Iong.
而你燃烧得非常耀眼，罗伊
And you have burnedso very, very brightIy, Roy.
看看你，你是天之骄子
Look at you.
You're the prodigaI son.
看看你，你是天之骄子
Look at you.
You're the prodigaI son.
你是个了不得的恩赐
You're quite a prize.
我做过...可议的事
I've done...
...questionabIe things.
我做过...可议的事
I've done...
...questionabIe things.
同时，也是不平凡的事
AIso extraordinary things.
...questionabIe things.
同时，也是不平凡的事
AIso extraordinary things.
享受你剩下的时间吧
ReveI in your time.
你想生化机械之主会让你上天堂吗?
Nothing the god of biomechanicswouIdn't Iet you in heaven for.
抱歉，赛巴斯汀
Sorry, Sebastian.
来吧，来吧
Come. Come.
和泰瑞一起的尸体是25岁的白种男性
Body identified with Tyrellis a 25-year-old male Caucasian.
姓名，赛巴斯汀，J.F.赛巴斯汀
Name: Sebastian, J.F. Sebastian.
地址：布拉德柏利公寓大厦，第九区N.F. 46751.
Address: Bradbury Apartments,Ninth Sector, NF4675 1.
我要你过去那里...
I want you to go down there and--
本区地面交通封闭你在这里做什么?
This sector's closed to ground traffic.What're you doing here?
- 我在工作，你要做什么?- 我现在要逮捕你
-I'm working. What are you doing?-Arresting you, that's what I'm doing.
我是德卡，银翼杀手，2-63-54我已备案及接受监督
I'm Deckard, BIade Runner.26354. I'm fiIed and monitored.
等等，正在查
Hold on. Checking.
好，确认无误，祝好运
Okay. Checked and cleared.Have a better one.
- 喂?- 嗨 J.F.在吗?
-Hello.-Hi. Is J.F. there?
- 你是哪位?- 艾迪，J.F.的老朋友
-Who is it?-This is Eddie, oId friend of J.F.'s.
这可不是对待朋友之道
That's no way to treat a friend.
Home again, home again, jiggidy-jig.
晚安，J.F.
Good evening, J.F.
Tea?
More tea?
向手无寸铁的对手开枪可不太光明正大
Not very sporting to fireon an unarmed opponent.
我以为你应该是个好人
I thought you weresupposed to be good.
你不是好人吗?
Aren't you the good man?
来吧！ 德卡
Come on, Deckard.
让我看看
Show me...
你有多少能耐
...what you're made of.
为自己骄傲吗，小个子?
Proud of yourseIf, IittIe man?
这是为了卓拉!
This is for Zhora.
这是为蒲莉丝
This is for Pris.
来吧，德卡
Come on, Deckard.
我就在这里但你要射直一点
I'm right here,but you've gotta shoot straight.
射直似乎还不够好!现在轮到我了
Straight doesn't seemto be good enough!
Now it's my turn.
射直似乎还不够好!现在轮到我了
Straight doesn't seemto be good enough!
我来之前会给你几秒钟的时间
I'm gonna give you a few secondsbefore I come.
一...二...
One.
Two.
一...二...
One.
Two.
三
Three.
四
Four.
蒲莉丝
Pris.
我来了!
I'm coming.
德卡!
Deckard!
四...五...
Four, five
要如何活下来?
How to stay alive?
我看到你了!
I can see you!
德卡，还不行
Not yet!
不...
Not... .
Five.
对了
Yes.
你最好振作一点
You better get it up.
不然我要杀了你
Or I'm gonna have to kiII you.
要是你死了你就没法玩了，如果你不玩...
UnIess you're aIive, you can't pIay.
And if you don't pIay... .
要是你死了你就没法玩了，如果你不玩...
UnIess you're aIive, you can't pIay.
And if you don't pIay... .
六，七!
Six, seven
下地狱或上天堂
Go to hell or go to heaven
很好! 就是这种精神!
Good, that's the spirit!
好痛
That hurt.
你真不理智
That was irrationaI of you.
更不用说...毫无运动精神
Not to mention...
...unsportsmanIike.
更不用说...毫无运动精神
Not to mention...
...unsportsmanIike.
你要去哪?
Where are you going?
活在恐惧中的体验还不错吧?
Quite an experience to Iive in fear,isn't it?
这就是做奴隶的滋味
That's what it is to be a sIave.
我所见过的事物
I've...
你们人类绝对无法置信
...seen thingsyou peopIe wouIdn't beIieve.
我目睹战船在猎户星座的端沿起火燃烧
Attack ships on fireoff the shouIder of Orion.
我看着C射线
I watched C-beams...
在唐怀瑟之门附近的黑暗中闪耀
...gIitter in the darknear the Tannh盲user Gate.
所有这些...时刻，终将流失...
AII those...
...moments wiII be Iost...
所有这些...时刻，终将流失...
AII those...
...moments wiII be Iost...
在时光中
...in time...
...moments wiII be Iost...
在时光中
...in time...
一如眼泪
...Iike...
...tears...
一如眼泪
...Iike...
...tears...
消失在雨中
...in rain.
死亡的时刻到了
Time to die.
你完成了男人的工作，阁下
You've done a man's job, sir.
我猜你做完了，嗯?
I guess you're through, huh?
完成了
Finished.
可惜她活不成了
It's too bad she won't Iive.
可是，谁能呢?
But then again, who does?
瑞秋?
RachaeI?
你爱我吗?
Do you Iove me?
我爱你
I Iove you.
你信任我吗?
Do you trust me?
我信任你
I trust you.
瑞秋?
RachaeI?
可惜她活不成了
It's too bad she won 't live.
可是，谁能呢?
But then again, who does?